KATE PRASOLEK

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio/

kate.prasolek@gmail.com 07479929600 London

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable digital designer with pro-active approach to tasks, great time management skills and can-do attitude. 8 years of design experience in a fast-paced, client-focused environment creating emails, websites, webpages and various assets. Self-learning advocate with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Creative mind with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography.

In July 2024 I started building an e-commerce shop centered around my passion for cardmaking. Digital design perfectly blends creativity and technology, combination of which I believe is key to my success. With my digital expertise, I'm excited to craft user experiences, build strong brand identities, and solve real-world problems through visually compelling and functional designs for you.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, UI/UX Design, Figma, Browserstack, Adobe XD, Git/Github, Bootstrap, CMS Email Design, Adobe Dreamweaver, Salesforce, Dotdigital, Litmus Adobe Photoshop, Adobe inDesign, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital & Graphic Designer at arteKatie Handmade (Jan 2020 - present) - personal project

- Build webpages, landing and product pages for e-commerce; create all campaigns assets.
- Ensure cohesive look and feel across all touchpoints and channels; build strong brand identity.
- Use multiple CMS to update information using AI; improve SEO; plan and schedule social media posts.
- Design and make market relevant handmade cards; product photography and photo retouching.
- Maintain assets libraries and files organised; keep track of sales and expenses.

Middleweight / Senior Digital Designer at Mention Me, London (Jul 2022 - Jul 2024)

- Create with HTML/ CSS referral demo websites for new clients based on website styling and imagery.
- Pro-actively enhance designs for conversion and performance by identifying improvement points.
- Prepare mock-ups, static assets and GIFs to present on design workshops to offer A/B tests.
- Conduct design workshops with stakeholders and clients presenting the improvement points.
- Style using CSS/HTML email templates created in MJML framework to resemble client's branding.
- Create Feefo banners using HTML/CSS; upload them using Github and perform live testing.
- QA Testing, ensuring compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all touchpoints including desktop, tablet and mobile websites, emails, corner peels, banners and styled links.
- Troubleshoot and solve client's queries by finding optimal visual and technical solution.
- Collaborate with ops, onboarding, and client success teams to deliver expected results within the SLA.

Digital Designer at Lidl GB, London (May 2021 - Jul 2022)

- Create homepages, landing pages, campaign pages in multiple CMS alongside all assets needed.
- Build weekly email newsletters, create still and animated assets and email templates.
- Work collaboratively with multiple teams for sign of and in a fast paced, deadline driven environment.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (Jan 2020 - May 2021)

• Website and email redesign proposals for various companies improving the UI & UX.

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create digital assets such as HTML emails, website banners, gifs, and social media imagery.
- Create print designs such as brochures, leaflets, magazine ads, and large-format prints.
- Work simultaneously on multiple digital and print projects, adhering to tight deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

• Create various print marketing collaterals and social media assets for diverse clients.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Receptionist and Data Entry Admin at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Sep 2017)

Reception duties and data administration.

Team Member & Shift Supervisor at Paul UK, London (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays, handling stock, sales plans, reporting and customer service.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel, Poland (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera, Poland (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, handling stock and deliveries, reporting.

Office & Administration Assistant at SALOS, Poland (Sep 2005 - Dec 2008)

Keeping the office organised, data entry.

INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

Can-do attitude	Attention to detail	Reliability	Time management
Ability to teamwork	Problem solving	Adaptiveness	Organisation skills
Communications skills	Strong creative eye	Prioritising	Enthusiasm

EDUCATION

2023 - 2024 Web Design: CSS, HTML & Bootstrap W3School certification.

2016 - 2021 Graphic Design, online learning.

2003 - 2008 Psychology, Silesian University, masters.